<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on People Analytics Lab (PAL) @ Nicholls</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on People Analytics Lab (PAL) @ Nicholls</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>4 things you must know on R</title>
      <link>/post/2021-05-02-4-basic-r/4_things_r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021-05-02-4-basic-r/4_things_r/</guid>
      <description>Author: Sandesh Sharma
Installing Packages and LibrariesLibraries are the things that make R so powerful. It is the heart for all processes that take place in R studio. CRAN (The Comprehensive R Archive Network) has more than 10,000 packages[1]. I think libraries/packages in R are like pre-built function that can be used by anyone, so they do not have to write the code from bottom up. Some of the famous libraries-that you may have heard, are ‘tidyverse’, ‘caret’, ‘ggplot’ etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research that is not reproducible is like pollution: We should treat it as such</title>
      <link>/post/2019-03-20-reproducible/reproducible/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-03-20-reproducible/reproducible/</guid>
      <description>When a measure becomes a target, it ceases to be a good measure - Goodhart’s law
I was recently interviewed by Vinay Patel and Joe Meyer of Louisiana Tech University (shout out to the Bulldogs!) on the topic of open science in IO psychology. In their article titled “We want open science in I-O!…Do we?” Vinay and Joe gave a broad overview of what open science is and why it particularly relevant for IO psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Wins in the PAL</title>
      <link>/post/2019-01-06-small-wins-in-the-pal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-01-06-small-wins-in-the-pal/</guid>
      <description>Author : Dr. Christopher CastilleThis year, we, Ann-Marie Castille (my better half over in the Computer Information Systems Department here at NSU and fellow I/O psychologist) and I founded the People Analytics Lab @ NSU. It is a social science lab that gives students opportunities to learn how to conduct research as it relates to organizational life. Thus far, there have been a few positive outcomes. One that I am particularly proud of involves a few students in our lab (Sarah Avet, Kathryn Daigle, and Bernard Wazeman).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
